feels like for you first of all to be
back in Washington?
>> Oh man, it's it's it's amazing. You
know, I'm I'm glad to be back. Uh
somewhere that I wanted to be. Uh I kind
of missed it. I you know, I I miss being
here and I'm excited to be back.
>> What was the last year like for you in
Jacksonville?
>> Oh man, it was it was it was a great
experience for me. Uh I went out there,
I learned a lot. Uh got to learn from
some people. Uh, and I think
Jacksonville was a place for where I had
to see myself grow in a different way.
Uh, you know, dealt with a little bit
of, uh, adversity, but at the end of the
day, it was all still good,
>> Nicki. Thanks.
>> Hi, Dami. Welcome back. Um, in what ways
do you think you've grown as a receiver?
>> Uh, really just just mentally. Uh, you
know, I kind of I understand the game a
little bit more than than what I've what
I've have in the past. Uh I I took the
steps to to learn from other people like
uh Jacobe Meyers, uh BTJ out there. Uh
and I had some people that that helped
me around even even the quarterback
Trevor, you know, uh just learning from
him uh that kind of took took the game
into another level and a different uh
viewpoint for me.
>> And then have you know just in coming
back did any of the guys reach out to
you once they heard like did Terry reach
out and then you know also what do what
do you think of the changes to the
building? The locker room wasn't
renovated, I don't think, when you left,
right?
>> Oh, yeah. No, it wasn't. Uh, so, uh, I
spoke with a few of the guys. Uh, I
spoke with, uh, Lil Mikey, uh, stand
still. Uh, I talked to Jaden, of course,
uh, talked to Terry. So, just, you know,
I always communicate with those guys,
even, you know, throughout the season
last year, you know, just to check in
and see how they were doing. But, oh
man, just coming back and seeing how
everything look way different than when
I was here before. Like, the locker room
does look amazing. uh you know it's kind
of separated from
man it's a lot of growth that that came
uh to the facility so and that's pretty
cool
>> David Harrison.
>> Hey Dei welcome back happy to see you
again
>> kind of going through the free agency
process when did it kind of become a
reality for you that Washington could be
on the table for you to make your
return? Uh, so the the process for me,
uh, and I I really just let my agent
handle everything. I I trust him, you
know, I mean, it's kind of his job and
and I trust him to, you know, put me in
a position that that's that can help me.
Uh, at the end of the day, I I just
wanted to stay on stay on the grind,
keep working and be prepared for
wherever I was going. And, uh, you know,
so it was just like, hey, Washington is,
you know, you it could be your
potential. And I was like, "Hey, let's
make it happen." Because for me, I I I
wanted to be back. I wanted to come back
and it got done.
>> Absolutely. Happy for you, too. And
David Blouse stepping up to be the
offensive coordinator. What kind of
expectations do you have? I know it's so
early, but as of right now, what kind of
expectations do you have for what that
offense is going to look like?
>> Oh, man. The sky's is the limit for
that. Uh Blau, he's he's very smart, you
know, and he he understand the game a
lot. Uh he played it, coached in it. uh
he was he was up under some great OC's
along the way and uh you know I think
for him I'm I'm really excited for for
what he has in store for for this place
here and uh you know I I don't doubt him
at all you know cuz hey I'm sure he can
get it done and and I'm going be
trusting him as as he's going to be
trusting us along the way. So I'm pretty
and and I'm happy for him that he even
you know got the job to expose himself
as well. So we're looking forward to
pretty good things this year.
Thanks, Dei. Welcome back.
>> Thank you,
>> Donna.
>> Well, welcome back, Deami.
>> Thank you. Thank you.
>> So, so um who would you say Deami Brown
is coming back this second time because
you left with a splash in those last
three three playoff games in 2024?
>> Uh yeah. So, I'm better than ever.
That's who Dami is. He's better than
ever. Uh, I've I've learned so much and
I've grown so much. Uh, mentally,
physically, you know, things things that
I probably wouldn't think I would be
previously before, you know, just and
age probably has something to do with
it. Just the mindset of growing. And I I
think for me is still to to go out there
and dominate and be the best person of
me, you know, best version of me every
single day being 1% better and continue
to grow because
and there's no age limit to where you
can stop learning. So and and that's
what I'm going to do. I'm going to keep
working. I'm going keep learning and I'm
going to be the person that I want to
be.
>> And you also said just a little while
ago that you miss being here. What did
you miss most about being here in
Washington as you reconnect with some of
your former teammates?
>> Oh man, it it was definitely those guys
the most. Uh, you know, it's,
you know, as as you build a brotherhood,
you build a bond with with a lot of the
guys and you communicate with a lot of
guys, you know, you kind of miss the
feeling of being around them. Uh, I
think the sport of football does that or
any team sport does that. you know, you
kind of have a connection with people
that that you know, you grow love with,
you work hard together with, you did
things together. And I think at the end
of the day, it's how much we bonded that
kind of like, oh man, you know, like I
miss those guys or I I missed even
growing up in the area like, man, I miss
home and I felt like there was a part a
part of home that was missing. So coming
back just it made a whole lot of sense
for me.
>> Well, congratulations and welcome back
home. Thank you,
>> Ben.
>> Hey, Dami. Welcome back. Um, any sense
of you just this is all that's
happening, but any sense of your role or
how you kind of how they kind of see you
this year similar to last time or what
do you think?
>> Uh, not yet. Uh, no. I'm, you know, I
will get to that point when it comes.
Uh, you know, but I think at the end of
the day is I just me going out there and
competing, you know, finding a way to
make the team better as well. Uh cuz at
the end of the day, I need them just
like how they need me. Uh we're going to
go out there, we're going to compete
together, we're going to make each other
better. And that's the only thing that
we're looking forward to right now. So
the the road part will come along the
way. Uh we'll figure that one out. So
right now, we just, you know, want to
set the set the tone and the standard
for where we want to go.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you,
>> Candy.
>> Hi, Bammy. Welcome back.
>> Hey, thank you.
You're welcome. So, you mentioned a
moment ago about um some of the
adversity that you experienced. So, can
you share a bit more about how you just
dealt with that adversity?
>> Um, so for me, uh, so I I had just just
a lot of a lot of small like mental
things that that kind of, you know, took
place around the time. And then uh I had
uh one one major in injury uh early on
in the season that kind of took place.
Uh but at the you know just dealing with
those things and having people that you
know that I can go to to to talk to
about just anything uh having people
that I can trust and then even you know
working myself back. Um I think that
right there you know just taking the
time to really self-evaluate you know
that's that's something that that that
really helped as well. And I think just
at the end of the day when when you're
really going through something and you
need to, you know, bounce back, you
know, always find people that that you
can talk to, you know, and just trust
the process along the way as well.
>> And as we're in the offseason and kind
of going from here to OTAAS, what do you
want to be working on?
>> Just getting stronger, faster, and just
being a competitor because that's what I
want to be. I want to compete. I want to
be the one that, you know, that people
can call on. So that's what I'm be
working on.
>> Thank you. Welcome back.
>> Thank you.
>> Appreciate the Thank you.
>> All right.
>> Thanks, Dami. Thanks.
>> Okay, you're good.
>> Cool. Yeah.